{
    "1": {
        "question": "You're 4th place right now in a race. What place will you be in when you pass the person in 3rd place?",
        "options": {
            "a": "1st",
            "b": "2nd",
            "c": "3rd",
            "d": "None of the above"
        },
        "answer": "c"
    },
    "2": {
        "question": "How many months have 28 days?",
        "options": {
            "a": "2",
            "b": "1",
            "c": "All of them",
            "d": "Depends if there's a leap year or not"
        },
        "answer": "c" 
    }
    ,
    "3": {
        "question": "The answer is really big. ",
        "options": {
            "a": "THE ANSWER.",
            "b": "Really big.",
            "c": "An elephant.",
            "d": "The data given is insufficient."
        },
        "answer": "a" 
    },
    "4": {
        "question": "Divide 30 by half and add ten. ",
        "options": {
            "a": "40.5",
            "b": "50",
            "c": "70",
            "d": "I know this is a trick question, so NONE. Ha!"
        },
        "answer": "c" 
    },
    "5": {
        "question": "There are two clocks of different colors: The green clock is broken and doesn't run at all, but the yellow clock loses one second every 24 hours. Which clock is more accurate? ",
        "options": {
            "a": "The green clock",
            "b": "The yellow clock",
            "c": "Neither",
            "d": "Both"
        },
        "answer": "a" 
    },
    "6": {
        "question": "Who is responsible to measure the Project’s performance?",
        "options": {
            "a": "Scrum Master",
            "b": "Delivery Manager",
            "c": "Development Team",
            "d": "Product Owner"
        },
        "answer": "d" 
    },
    "7": {
        "question": "What is a Sprint Review?",
        "options": {
            "a": "Activity to Introspect and Adapt",
            "b": "Activity to improve Scrum Processes",
            "c": "Activity to plan for the next Sprint",
            "d": "Activity to plan for the release"
        },
        "answer": "a" 
    },
    "8": {
        "question": "Who should necessarily attend the Daily Standup meeting?",
        "options": {
            "a": "The Scrum Team",
            "b": "The Development Team",
            "c": "The Development Team and the Product Owner",
            "d": "The Scrum Team and the Stakeholders"
        },
        "answer": "b" 
    },
    "9": {
        "question": "How many pillars does sikes hall have?",
        "options": {
            "a": "6",
            "b": "9",
            "c": "7",
            "d": "8"
        },
        "answer": "d" 
    },
    "10": {
        "question": "What are Clemsons main colors?",
        "options": {
            "a": "Orange",
            "b": "Purple",
            "c": "White",
            "d": "All of them"
        },
        "answer": "d" 
    },
    "11":{
        "question": "What is Clemson main library name?",
        "options": {
            "a": "Gunnin Architecture Library",
            "b": "R.M Cooper Library",
            "c": "Clemson Library",
            "d": "None of the above"
        },
        "answer": "b"
    },
    "12": {
        "question": "Who is Clemson Football head coach?",
        "options": {
            "a": "Dabo Swinney",
            "b": "Mario Critobal",
            "c": "Dave Doeren",
            "d": "None of the above"
        },
        "answer": "a" 
    },
    "13":{
        "question": "What brand sponsors Clemson?",
        "options": {
            "a": "Adidas",
            "b": "Under Armor",
            "c": "Puma",
            "d": "Nike"
        },
        "answer": "d"  
    },
    "14":{
        "question": "What is the Clemson motto?",
        "options": {
            "a": "Who shall separate us now?",
            "b": "Reach for the Stars",
            "c": "For the Land and its People",
            "d": "The spirit makes the master"
        },
        "answer": "d"  
    },
    "15":{
        "question": "The Clemson Tigers are based in which American state?",
        "options": {
            "a": "New York State",
            "b": "Virginia",
            "c": "Colorado",
            "d": "South Carolina"
        },
        "answer": "d"  
    },
    "16":{
        "question": "The home field of the Clemson Tigers football team is known by what nickname?",
        "options": {
            "a": "Death Valley",
            "b": "Hell's Kitchen",
            "c": "Easy Street",
            "d": "Struggle Street"
        },
        "answer": "a"   
    },
    "17":{
        "question": "What is P.A.W",
        "options": {
            "a": "Passionate About Winning",
            "b": "Purpose, Aspiration, and Wisdom",
            "c": "Positively Aiming for Success",
            "d": "Profoundly Ambitious Winners"
        },
        "answer": "a"   
    },
    "18":{
        "question": "Who is the world’s biggest producer of oil?",
        "options": {
            "a": "Saudi Arabia",
            "b": "United States",
            "c": "Canada",
            "d": "United Arab Emirates"
        },
        "answer": "b"   
    },
    "19":{
        "question": "Where would you find the world’s largest desert?",
        "options": {
            "a": "Saudi Arabia",
            "b": "China",
            "c": "Egypt",
            "d": "Antartica"
        },
        "answer": "d"   
    },
    "20":{
        "question": "What element is the periodic number 19, highlighted by the letter K?",
        "options": {
            "a": "Potassium",
            "b": "Sodium",
            "c": "Krypton",
            "d": "Nickel"
        },
        "answer": "a"   
    }

}